Guide to the Peter Palmquist Collection of Women in Photography
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographic Materials, 1971-2003; Series II; (222 boxes)
  - Photographic Materials, (117 boxes)
    - Vance, Harriet S., Miss (born 1867), 1 photographic print (Box 313, Folder 2373)
    - Vane Percy, Grace (born 1981), 3 photographic prints and 3 color photographic prints (Box 313, Folder 2374)
    - Vaughan, Caroline (born 1949), 1 serial (Box 313, Folder 2375)
    - Vepstas, Constance, 4 color 35mm slides (Box 313, Folder 2376)
      Also known as Connie Vepstas
    - Verseput, Deborah Ruth (born 1958), 1 color photographic print (Box 313, Folder 2377)
      Also known as Deborah Russell or Debbie Verseput
    - Viall, Matilda, Mrs. (born 1854), 2 photographic prints (Box 313, Folder 2378)
      Also known as Mrs. Frank M. Viall
    - Villines, Carrie (born 1973), 3 color 35mm slides (Box 313, Folder 2379)
    - Voelcker, Elsa (born 1948), 92 color 35mm slides (Box 313, Folder 2380)
    - Vogelsang, E., Frau, 2 photographic prints (Box 328, Folder 2381)
    - Von Eckardt, Barbara, 9 color 35mm slides (Box 328, Folder 2382)
    - Voorheis, E. G., Mrs., 1 album (7 photographic prints) (Box 328)
    - Vorbeck, Henriette, 3 photographic prints (Box 328, Folder 2383)
    - Vreeland, Rosa, Mrs. (born 1853), 12 photographic prints (Box 328, Folder 2384)
      Also known as Mrs. Vreeland-Whitlock
    - Waddell, Myra, Miss, 1 photographic print (Box 328, Folder 2385)
    - Waddington, Julia, 2 photographic prints (Box 328, Folder 2386)
    - Wade, Frances A., Miss, 4 photographic prints (Box 328, Folder 2387)
    - Wagy, Alta F., 1 photographic print (Box 328, Folder 2388)
    - Wahlstrom, Amanda, 1 photographic print (Box 328, Folder 2389)
    - Wahlström, Selinda, 9 photographic prints (Box 328, Folder 2390)
    - Waite, Shayla, 4 color 35mm slides (Box 328, Folder 2391)
    - Waldack, Mary, Mrs. (born circa 1849), 12 photographic prints (Box 328, Folder 2392)
      Also known as Mrs. Charles Waldack or Mrs. Charles Waldach
    - Walker, Cheryl (born 1958), 10 color 35mm slides (Box 328, Folder 2393)
    - Walker, Diana (born 1942), 1 color photographic print (Box 328, Folder 2394)
    - Walker, Maxine, 1 serial (Box 328, Folder 2395)
    - Wallén, Annie, 1 photographic print (Box 328, Folder 2396)
    - Waller, E. K., 1 photographic print (Box 328, Folder 2397)
    - Wallgren, Therése, 6 photographic prints (Box 328, Folder 2398)
    - Wallin, Amanda, 2 photographic prints (Box 328, Folder 2399)
    - Wallin, Hanna, 1 photographic print (Box 328, Folder 2400)
    - Wanless, Mary Dorsey, 2 color 35mm slides (Box 328, Folder 2401)
    - Ward, Catharine Weed Barnes, Mrs. (1851-1913), 26 photographic prints, 2 serials, and 1 dust jacket (Box 328, Folder 2402)
      Also known as Catharine Weed Barnes or Mrs. H. Snowden Ward,
    - Ward, Susan, Mrs. (born circa 1838), 8 photographic prints (Box 328, Folder 2403)
      Also known as Mrs. Henry Ward
    - Ward, W. Blanch, 1 photographic print (Box 328, Folder 2404)
    - Warfield, Joanne (born 1943), 2 color photographic prints, 9 color 35mm slides, and 1 serial (Box 328, Folder 2405)
    - Warman, Orvetta (born 1919), 1 color photographic print (Box 329, Folder 2406)
      Also known as Mrs. George Warman
    - Warner, B. E., Miss, 1 photographic print (Box 329, Folder 2407)
    - Warnström, Systrarna, 5 photographic prints (Box 329, Folder 2408)
    - Wasmann, Vilhelmine, 1 photographic print (Box 329, Folder 2409)
    - Waterman, Jill (born 1958), 21 color 35mm slides and 6 magnets (Box 329, Folder 2410)
    - Waterman, Sally (born 1974), 10 color 35mm slides (Box 329, Folder 2411)
    - Watkins, Laura J., Mrs. (born circa 1833), 19 photographic prints (Box 329, Folder 2412)
      Also known as Laura J. Broughton, Hill & Watkins, or Mrs. Benjamin Watkins
    - Watson, Cornelia Knox (1864-1930), 5 photographic prints (Box 329, Folder 2413)
      Also known as Cornelia Ann Bernard or Cornelia A. Knox
    - Watson, Denise Rehse, 4 color 35mm slides (Box 329, Folder 2414)
    - Watson, Mabel A., Miss (born circa 1881), 2 photographic prints (Box 329, Folder 2415)
    - Weaver, Anna K., 1 color photographic print (Box 329, Folder 2416)
    - Webster, Annie Jane, Miss, 2 photographic prints (Box 329, Folder 2417)
    - Wehrstein, Karen, 3 color photographic prints (Box 329, Folder 2418)
    - Weigel, Mary (1858-1934), 1 photographic print and 4 color photographic prints (Box 329, Folder 2419)
    - Weil, Mathilde (born 1872), 1 photographic print (Box 329, Folder 2420)
    - Weld, James A., Mrs., 2 photographic prints (Box 329, Folder 2421)
      Also known as Mrs. Jas. A. Weld
    - Wells, Catherine J., Mrs., 2 photographic prints (Box 329, Folder 2422)
      Also known as Mrs. C. D. Wells or Mrs. C. F. Wells
    - Wells, Margaret Harrington (born circa 1858), 1 photographic print (Box 329, Folder 2423)
      Also known as Wells & Lady
    - Westbrook, Sarah M., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 329, Folder 2424)
    - Wetterberg, Lisa, 1 photographic print (Box 329, Folder 2425)
    - Weymouth, Etta Mae (circa 1883-1970), 57 photographic prints (Box 329, Folder 2426)
    - Whaley, Jo (born 1953), 39 color 35mm slides and 1 serial (Box 329, Folder 2427)
    - Wheeler, Cece, 3 color 35mm slides (Box 329, Folder 2428)
    - Wheeler, Hattie L., Mrs. (born circa 1860), 1 photographic print (Box 329, Folder 2429)
      Also known as Mrs. Alva Wheeler
    - Whitaker, Corinne, 3 color 35mm slides (Box 329, Folder 2430)
    - Whitcomb, Laine (born 1944), 2 color 35mm slides (Box 329, Folder 2431)
    - White, Miss, 2 photographic prints (Box 329, Folder 2432)
      Also known as Misses White & Hubbell
    - White, Etta P., Mrs. (born circa 1835), 1 photographic print (Box 329, Folder 2433)
      Also known as E. P. White
    - White, L., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 329, Folder 2434)
    - White, Patricia (born 1946), 2 serials (Box 329, Folder 2435)
      Also known as Patty White
    - White, Sylvia (born 1946), 6 color 35mm slides (Box 329, Folder 2436)
    - Whitmore, Charlotte (born 1947), 1 photographic print, 1 color photographic print, and 4 color 35mm slides (Box 329, Folder 2437)
    - Widgrén, Julia Viktorina Rosalie (1842-1917), 5 photographic prints (Box 329, Folder 2438)
    - Widholm, Maria, 1 photographic print (Box 329, Folder 2439)
    - Wiesler, Patricia, 1 photographic print and 1 color inkjet print (Box 329, Folder 2440)
    - Wigand, Ottilie, 1 photographic print (Box 329, Folder 2441)
    - Wiggins, Myra Albert (1869-1956), 1 photographic print and 1 serial (Box 329, Folder 2442)
      Also known as Myra Albert
    - Wigholm, Hedvig, 1 photographic print (Box 329, Folder 2443)
    - Wightman, M., Mrs., 3 photographic prints (Box 329, Folder 2444)
    - Wikström, Constance, 3 photographic prints (Box 329, Folder 2445)
    - Wikström, Maria, 1 photographic print (Box 329, Folder 2446)
    - Wilcox, Ida Mabel (1894-1947), 1 photographic print (Box 330, Folder 2447)
    - Wilde, Augusta (born circa 1832), 3 photographic prints (Box 330, Folder 2448)
    - Wilder, Clara Burt, 1 photographic print (Box 330, Folder 2449)
      Also known as Mrs. C. J. Wilder
    - Wilder, Holly L., 1 color 35mm slide (Box 330, Folder 2450)
    - Willcutt, Amelia B., Mrs. (born circa 1845), 1 photographic print (Box 330, Folder 2451)
    - Willett, Cora, 2 photographic prints (Box 330, Folder 2452)
    - Willford, Betty Decker (1917-2004), 5 photographic prints and 1 postcard (Box 330, Folder 2453)
    - Williams, Elizabeth (born 1924), 5 photographic prints (Box 330, Folder 2454)
      Also known as Tex Williams
    - Williams, H. R., Mrs., 6 photographic prints (Box 330, Folder 2455)
      Also known as Mrs. L. M. Williams
    - Williams, Jane, 1 album (33 photographic prints) (Box 330)
    - Williams, Jane, 1 photographic print (Box 330, Folder 2456)
    - Williams, Ruby, 1 book (Box 330, Folder 2457)
    - Williams, Sarah, Mrs. (born circa 1826), 12 photographic prints (Box 330, Folder 2458)
    - Williamson, Hanna, 1 photographic print (Box 330, Folder 2459)
    - Willis, Mrs., 2 photographic prints (Box 330, Folder 2460)
    - Wilson, Amelia Decker, 1 photographic print (Box 330, Folder 2461)
    - Wilson, Joyce, 1 serial (Box 330, Folder 2462)
    - Wilson, Julia Marianne, Mrs. (born circa 1850), 4 photographic prints (Box 330, Folder 2463)
    - Wilson, Lawrence, Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 330, Folder 2464)
    - Wilson, Lillian Elaine (born 1963), 2 color 35mm slides (Box 330, Folder 2465)
    - Wilson, Maude Jay, Miss, 1 photographic print (Box 330, Folder 2466)
    - Wilson, Patricia (born 1954), 3 color photographic prints (Box 330, Folder 2467)
    - Wimermark, A. H., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 330, Folder 2468)
    - Wimermark, Pauline, Mrs., 7 photographic prints (Box 330, Folder 2469)
    - Winell, Anna, 5 photographic prints (Box 330, Folder 2470)
    - Wingate, Jane (born 1942), 1 serial (Box 330, Folder 2471)
    - Winslow, Mary, Mrs. (born circa 1870), 2 photographic prints (Box 330, Folder 2472)
    - Winters, Mary V., 1 photographic print (Box 330, Folder 2473)
    - Wintler, Hazel M., 1 photographic print (Box 330, Folder 2474)
    - Wisner, Anna, Miss, 1 photographic print (Box 330, Folder 2475)
    - Withington, Eliza W. (circa 1825-1877), 3 tintypes, 4 stereographs, 75 photographic prints, 10 color photographic prints, 12 color inkjet prints, and 50 35mm film negatives (Box 331, Folder 2476-2485)
    - Wittberg, Olivia, 4 photographic prints (Box 330, Folder 2486)
    - Wolf, J., Mrs., 3 photographic prints (Box 330, Folder 2487)
    - Wolf, Linda Ann (born 1950), 1 photographic print (Box 330, Folder 2488)
    - Wolfe, Leanna (born 1953), 5 color 35mm slides (Box 330, Folder 2489)
    - Woodcock, Catherine, Mrs. (born circa 1862), 1 photographic print (Box 330, Folder 2490)
      Also known as Mrs. Francis A. Woodcock
    - Woodward, R. J., Mrs., 3 photographic prints (Box 330, Folder 2491)
    - Woodworth, Ruby M. Thorp, Mrs. (born 1842), 13 photographic prints (Box 330, Folder 2492)
      Also known as Miss R. M. Thorp or Mrs. J. P. Woodworth
    - Wootten, Bayard Morgan, Mrs. (1875-1959), 1 photographic print and 1 catalog (Box 330, Folder 2493)
    - Worth, Sarah A., Mrs. (born circa 1833), 2 photographic prints (Box 330, Folder 2494)
      Also known as Mrs. S. A. Worth
    - Worthing, Hanna H., Mrs., 2 photographic prints (Box 330, Folder 2495)
    - Woten, Pearl E., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 332, Folder 2496)
      Also known as Mrs. W. D. Campbell
    - Wotkyns, Elizabeth B., Miss, 1 photographic print (Box 332, Folder 2497)
      Also known as Miss Elizabeth B. Wotkyne
    - Wright, Cora, 1 photographic print (Box 332, Folder 2498)
    - Wright, Mary L., Mrs., 2 photographic prints (Box 332, Folder 2499)
      Also known as Mrs. William R. Wright
    - Wuebker, Mary Ann, 1 photographic print (Box 332, Folder 2500)
    - Wuthrich, Emma (1849-1889), 1 photographic print (Box 332, Folder 2501)
    - Wyatt, Mary J., Mrs. (born 1843), 24 photographic prints (Box 332, Folder 2502)
      Also known as Mrs. Andrew A. Wyatt, Mrs. M. J. Wyatt, or Mrs. M. J. Wyatts
    - Wykes, Elmira S., Mrs. (born circa 1826), 1 photographic print (Box 332, Folder 2503)
    - Wyman, Ida (born 1926), 1 serial (Box 332, Folder 2504)
    - Yant, G. A., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 332, Folder 2505)
    - Yates, Kathy, 1 color 35mm slide (Box 332, Folder 2506)
    - Yates, Lillian (circa 1860-1942), 5 photographic prints (Box 332, Folder 2507)
      Also known as Yates Sisters
    - Yeager, Bunny (born 1930), 1 photographic print (Box 332, Folder 2508)
    - Ylla (1911-1955), 1 photographic print and 2 serials (Box 332, Folder 2509)
      Also known as Camilla Koffler
    - Yoshida, Barbara (born 1945), 1 serial (Box 332, Folder 2510)
    - Young, Agnes C., Miss (born 1853), 1 photographic print (Box 332, Folder 2511)
    - Young, Sarah J. (born 1848), 6 photographic prints (Box 332, Folder 2512)
      Also known as S. J. Young
    - Zacharskiego, Józefa, 1 photographic print (Box 332, Folder 2513)
    - Zätterlöf, Olga, 4 photographic prints (Box 332, Folder 2514)
    - Zetterström, Anna, 3 photographic prints (Box 332, Folder 2515)
    - Zordich, Cynthia (born 1963), 1 photographic print and 7 color 35mm slides (Box 332, Folder 2516)
    - Zucchello, Paola, 3 color 35mm slides (Box 332, Folder 2517)
    - Zumbrun, Heidi (born 1965), 1 color 35mm slide (Box 332, Folder 2518)
    - Zusman, Barbara (born 1944), 1 color photographic print (Box 332, Folder 2519)
    - [No Surname], Rosie, 2 photographic prints (Box 332, Folder 2520)
    - Unidentified woman photographer, 700 photographic prints (Box 333, Folder 2521-2548)
      International travel photography by an unidentified woman photographer, 1900-1923
    - Unidentified women photographers, 5 photographic prints and 1 color photographic print (Box 332, Folder 2549)
      Photographic prints found in collection without any attributed photographer
  - Photograph Albums, (49 boxes)
    50 albums (6538 photographic prints)
    This subseries consists of photograph albums and scrapbooks of various sizes created by women photographers. Each album is housed in an individual box.
    A few albums of smaller dimensions and thicknesses are arranged within in the Photographic Materials subseries.
    - Atkinson, Florence E., 1 album (56 photographic prints) (Box 334)
    - Bigelow, Mary Jane Budd, 1 album (129 photographic prints) (Box 335)
    - Brogden, Penny (born 1944), 2 albums (23 photographic prints) (Box 336-337)
    - Brown, Arthur Merrill, Mrs., 3 albums (568 photographic prints) (Box 338-340)
    - Burman, Hazel W., Mrs., 2 albums (190 photographic prints) (Box 341-342)
      Also known as Mrs. Robert A. Burman
    - Carr, Miss, 2 albums (453 photographic prints) (Box 343-344)
    - Coombs, Callie M., Miss (1873-1927), 1 album (148 photographic prints) (Box 345)
    - Eisemann, Hortense, 1 album (271 photographic prints) (Box 346)
    - Filippini, Mrs., 1 album (161 photographic prints) (Box 347)
    - Flint, Muriel Beardsley, Miss (born circa 1903), 2 albums (568 photographic prints) (Box 348-349)
      Also known as Mrs. Arthur Hill Gilbert
    - Frohnecke, Elfriede (1881-1972), 1 album (224 photographic prints) (Box 350)
    - Garrett, Edna M., Mrs. (born 1874), 1 album (180 photographic prints) (Box 351)
    - Geldert, Eleanor F., 1 album (185 photographic prints) (Box 352)
    - Hart, Dora, 1 album (19 photographic prints) (Box 353)
    - Heim, Johanna E. (born 1887), 1 album (25 photographic prints) (Box 354)
    - Horn, Grace Chandler (1879-1967), 1 album (14 photographic prints) (Box 355)
    - Jones, Helene Marie, 1 album (100 photographic prints) (Box 356)
    - Kegg, Cora E., 3 albums (65 photographic prints) and 1 notebook (Box 357-360)
    - Krei, La Verne J., Mrs., 1 album (98 photographic prints) (Box 361)
    - Lindsey, Inez Moore, 1 album (88 photographic prints) (Box 362)
      Also known as Inez Moore
    - McKellar, Agnes, 2 albums (176 photographic prints) (Box 363-364)
    - Rathjen, Jane, Mrs. (born circa 1846), 1 album (90 photographic prints) (Box 365)
    - Schweiz, Ina, 1 album (98 photographic prints) (Box 366)
    - Tice, Frankie, Miss (1886-1979), 2 albums (915 photographic prints) (Box 367-368)
      Also known as Ada F. Tice
    - Tilghmann, Anna S., 1 album (199 photographic prints) (Box 369)
    - Treat, Marcia C. Griffin, Mrs. (1872-1964), 2 albums (426 photographic prints) (Box 370-371)
      Also known as Mrs. Charles H. Treat or Baroness Frederick Von Reichenberg,
    - Valentine, B., 1 album (152 photographic prints) (Box 372)
    - Weiss, Helen, 1 album (120 photographic prints) (Box 373)
    - Wentzel, Gladys, Miss, 1 album (102 photographic prints) (Box 374)
    - [No Surname], Marion, 1 album (230 photographic prints) (Box 375)
  - Cased Photographs and Fragile Photographic Materials, (10 boxes)
    This subseries is organized in four sections according to physical format: cased photographs, glass negatives, lantern slides, and framed photographic prints.
    This subseries consists of fragile photographic materials created by women photographers.
    - Cased photographs
      - Balch, Eliza, 1 ambrotype (Box 376, Folder 2550)
      - La Nina, 2 daguerreotypes (Box 376, Folder 2551-2552)
      - Ramsauer, Malvina Antoinette Thompson (circa 1818-1890), 9 ambrotypes and 1 daguerreotypes (Box 376, Folder 2553-2562)
        Includes daguerreotype portrait of Ramsauer by Charles J. Quinby
      - Reed, Candace McCormick, Mrs. (1818-1900), 1 daguerreotype (Box 377, Folder 2563)
      - Short, Ruth, Mrs., 2 daguerreotypes (Box 377, Folder 2564-2565)
        Also known as Mrs. S. P. Short
      - Wilde, Augusta (born circa 1832), 1 daguerreotype (Box 377, Folder 2566)
      - Williams, H. R., Mrs., 1 ambrotype (Box 377, Folder 2567)
        Also known as
      - Withington, Eliza W. (circa 1825-1877), 4 ambrotypes and 1 medal (Box 377, Folder 2568-2572)
    - Glass negatives
      - Cardozo, Abigail E. (1864-1937), 1 glass negative (Box 378, Folder 2573)
      - Crane, Stella, 25 glass negatives (Box 378, Folder 2574-2598)
      - Cropley, Juliette C., Miss, 99 glass negatives (Box 379, Folder 2599-2697)
      - Lyons, Katherine G., Miss, 13 glass negatives (Box 380, Folder 2698-2710)
      - Medlar, Hazel, 10 glass negatives (Box 381, Folder 2711-2720)
      - Stockbridge, Nellie Jane (1868-1965), 2 glass negatives (Box 381, Folder 2721-2722)
    - Lantern slides
      - Baker, Edith M., Mrs. (1872-1952), 7 lantern slides (Box 382, Folder 2723-2729)
      - Karge, Annette (born circa 1898), 1 lantern slide (Box 382, Folder 2730)
      - Miller, Mrs., 1 lantern slide (Box 382, Folder 2731)
      - Pinkerton, Charlotte M., 6 lantern slides (Box 382, Folder 2732-2737)
      - Taylor Ray, Dorothy, 2 lantern slides (Box 382, Folder 2738-2739)
    - Framed photographic prints
      - Freeman, Emma B. (1880-1928), 2 framed photographic prints (Box 383, Folder 2740-2741)
      - Horn, Grace Chandler (1879-1967), 2 framed photographic prints and 2 photographs on porcelain (Box 384, Folder 2742-2743)
      - Jauirs, W.H., Mrs., 1 framed photographic print (Box 385)
  - Audiovisual Materials, (2 boxes)
    This subseries is organized in four sections according to physical format: audiotapes, moving film, videotapes, and CD-ROMs.
    This subseries consists of audiovisual materials created by or documenting work by women photographers. The CD-ROMs also include general works documenting women photographers.
    - Reel-to-reel audiotapes
      - Palfi, Marion. Slide tape, undated; 1; 01:54:16; A high amount of background noise can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. The tracks are muffled rom 29:53 until the end of the tape. (Box 386, Item barcode 39002104888426)
        Conditions Governing Access
        Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - Palfi, Marion. Womanspace (Los Angeles Woman's Building), 1973 December 12; 1; 01:02:10 (Box 386, Item barcode 39002104888434)
    - Motion picture film
      - Van Ronk, Marion, Dr. (circa 1911-2001), 6 8mm moving film reels and 1 16mm moving film reels (Box 386, Folder 2745-2751)
    - Videocassettes
      - Armer, Laura Adams, Mrs. (1874-1963). Navajo Mountain Chant, copy 3, Koenig 4/96, undated; WAMSSS2600_0001; 1; 00:51:43; There was a very low contrast transfer from film to video. (Box 386, Item barcode 39002093673052)
      - Campbell, Kathleen (born 1944). Modern Theology or A Universe of Our Own Creation, WAMSSS2600_0002; 1; 00:05:24 (Box 386, Item barcode 39002093673060)
    - CD-ROMs
      - Corinne, Tee A. (1943-2006), 1 CD-ROM (Box 386, Folder 2754)
      - Fournier, Collette V. (born 1952), 1 CD-ROM (Box 386, Folder 2755)
      - Horton, Nancy G. (born 1962), 1 CD-ROM (Box 386, Folder 2756)
      - Kerr, S. Hollis (born 1970), 1 CD-ROM (Box 386, Folder 2757)
      - Leghait, Louise, Madame, 1 CD-ROM (Box 386, Folder 2758)
        Also known as Madame L.
      - Traub, Barbara (born 1960), 1 CD-ROM (Box 386, Folder 2759)
      - Urminska, Natalia Maria, 2 CD-ROMs (Box 387, Folder 2760)
      - Warfield, Joanne (born 1943), 1 CD-ROM (Box 387, Folder 2761)
      - Women Artists of the American West, 1 CD-ROM (Box 387, Folder 2762)
        An internet course developed by Susan Ressler and Jerrold Maddox for Purdue University
      - Women in Documentary Photography 2000, 1 CD-ROM (Box 387, Folder 2763)
        Includes portfolio by eight women photographers in the Berenice Abbott Internationa Competition at the Springfield Museum of Art, Springfield, Ohio
      - Women in Photography International: Tea Time: Images of Women, Images of Tea, 2 CD-ROMs (Box 387, Folder 2764)
  - Oversize Photographic and Biographical Materials, 52; oversize boxes
    This subseries consists of photographic materials created by or documenting individual women photographers, biographical materials, and pieces of realia. Photographic material consists of vintage prints and copy photographs, and some associated publications, tear sheets, and ephemera that possess dimensions greater than 22 x 29 cm (8.7 x 11.4 in.).
    - Abbott, Berenice (1898-1991), 4 tear sheets and 1 serial (Box 388, Folder 2765)
    - Adam, Adrienne, 1 color photographic print (Box 388, Folder 2766)
    - Adams, Kelly Serat (born 1977), 2 photographic prints (Box 388, Folder 2767)
    - Aiken, Mary A. (1917-2005), 1 unbound scrapbook (98 photographic prints), 33 photographic prints, and 1 tear sheet (Box 389-390, Folder 2768-2800)
    - Albin Guillot, Laure, Mrs. (1879-1962), 1 book (Box 388, Folder 2801)
      Also known as Albin Guillot
    - Alexander-Clarke, Marsia, 1 serial (Box 388, Folder 2802)
    - Allport, Catherine, 2 color photographic prints (Box 388, Folder 2803)
      Also known as Catherine Gardiner Allport
    - Alt, Jane Fulton (born 1951), 1 photographic print (Box 388, Folder 2804)
    - Antes, J. K., Mrs., 1 tear sheet (Box 388, Folder 2805)
    - Arbus, Diane (1923-1971), 1 serial (Box 388, Folder 2806)
      Also known as Diane Nemerov Arbus or Diane Nemerov
    - Armer, Laura Adams, Mrs. (1874-1963), 6 photographic prints and 1 tear sheet (Box 391, Folder 2807)
    - Arnold, Harriet H., 2 serials (Box 388, Folder 2808)
    - Auerbach, Ellen (1906-2004), 1 serial (Box 388, Folder 2809)
      Also known as Ellen Rosenberg or Ringl & Pit
    - Aurell, Anette, 1 tear sheet (Box 388, Folder 2810)
    - Austen, Alice (1866-1952), 2 serials and 1 tear sheet (Box 388, Folder 2811)
      Also known as Elizabeth Alice Austen
    - Baruch, Ruth-Marion (1922-1997), 1 photographic print (Box 392, Folder 2812)
    - Beckwith, Carol (born 1945), 1 tear sheet (Box 392, Folder 2813)
    - Belknap, Hazel, 1 hand-colored photographic print (Box 392, Folder 2814)
    - Bell, Winter (1975-2003), 1 photographic print and 3 color photographic prints (Box 392, Folder 2815)
    - Bennett, Betty Nettis (1927-1996), 13 photographic prints and 1 color photographic print (Box 392, Folder 2816)
    - Bernstein, Arlene (born 1940), 2 photographic prints (Box 392, Folder 2817)
    - Berryhill, Gene, 1 color photographic print (Box 392, Folder 2818)
    - Biggerstaff, Candace, 1 color photographic print (Box 392, Folder 2819)
    - Bisbee, Mary L., Miss (born 1870), 1 serial (Box 392, Folder 2820)
    - Bonney, M. Thérèse (Mabel Thérèse) (1897-1978), 2 tear sheets and 10 serials (Box 393, Folder 2821)
    - Borken, Marian, 1 tear sheet (Box 392, Folder 2822)
    - Botkin, Liza Hennessey (born 1942), 1 photographic print (Box 392, Folder 2823)
    - Bourke-White, Margaret (1904-1971), 6 tear sheets and 19 serials (Box 394-395, Folder 2824-2833)